(Penny:)I only figured that out
(Penny:)because I've never heard
of any of them.
(Wil:)I deserve that.
(Wil:)I invited you on my show
and I drove here.
(Howard:)Sorry.
(Wil:)Okay, so, this is
basically gonna be
(Wil:)just like a little talk show.
(Wil:)Uh, we're gonna take some calls,
(Wil:)we'll talk about what
it was like on the set
of Serial Ape-ist 2.
(Wil:)It should be really fun.
(Leonard:)This is exciting.
Yeah.
(Penny:)So, how many people listen?
(Wil:)Most people download it later,
(Wil:)but usually a few thousand
people listen live.
What?! A few thousand people
(Penny:)listen to you talk
about nerd stuff?
(Wil:)Again, right in the ears,
(Wil:)straight to the feelings.
(Amy:)Can you please pass the salt?
(Leonard:)Sure.
(Sheldon:)It's not like I was invited
to Richard Feynman's house
(Sheldon:)and have anything better to do.
(Amy:)Is this how the rest
of the night's going to be?
(Sheldon:)I don't know the future.
(Sheldon:)Do you think there's a chance
(Sheldon:)that an asteroid
could hit the Earth,
(Sheldon:)destroying Feynman's house
and everyone in it?
(Amy:)No, Sheldon.